RG 015, Office of Policy and Management
Connecticut State Library
- Series 13. Comprehensive Planning Division, 1957-1991; 28 cubic feet
  - Community Development Block Grants, 1970-1977
    - 1970-1976, 1985-026B
      - CDA 7512CD02: Liberty St. Renewal Program (City of Ansonia) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7512CD03: Entitlement Grant (City of Ansonia) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7512CD04: Senior Center Housing Inventory & Needs Analysis (Town of Seymour) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7512CD04: Community Development Block Grant (Discretionary) - Second Program Year (Town of Groton) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7512CD06: Entitlement Grant (City of Derby) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7512CD07: Extend Central Sanitary Sewers to Valley View Neighborhood (City of Derby) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7512CD08: Loomis Heights Sewer Project (Town of New Hartford) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7601CD01: Revolving Loan Fund - Housing Rehabilitation (Town of Manchester) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7601CD02: Entitlement Grant (City of Bridgeport) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7601CD03: Community Development Discretionary Grant (City of Willimantic) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7601CD04: Community Development Discretionary Grant (Town of Plainfield) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7601CD05: New London Community Development Programs Entitlement Grant (City of New London) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7601CD06: Entitlement Grant (Town of Bloomfield) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7601CD07: Entitlement Grant (Town of East Hartford) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7601CD08: Site Acquisition - Elderly Housing (Town of Cheshire) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7601CD09: Community Development Block Grant Entitlement Funding - Year II (Town of Enfield) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7601CD10: Entitlement Grant (City of Norwalk) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7601CD11: Wilson Neighborhood Improvement (Town of Windsor) (Box 5)
      - CDA 7602CD01: Entitlement Grant (Town of Danbury) (Box 5)
      - CDA 7601CD02: Discretionary Grant (Town of Wallingford) (Box 5)
      - CDA 7602CD03: Community Development Block Grant Program - Entitlement Grant (City of Milford) (Box 5)
    - 1976-1977, 1986-010C
      Applications for Federal funds.
      - CDA 7603CD11: Community Development Block Grant Program - Second Year - Entitlement Grant (Town of Stratford) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7603CD12: Community Development Block Grant Program - Entitlement Grant (City of Meriden) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7603CD13: Community Development Act Entitlement Grant (Town of Fairfield) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7604CD01: Innovative Project - Neighborhood Preservation - FY 1976 (City of Bridgeport) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7604CD02: Community Development Block Grant Program - Entitlement Grant (City of Portland) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7604CD03: Community Development Block Grant Program - Second Year- Entitlement Grant (City of West Haven) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7604CD04: Second Year Entitlement Grant (Town of Greenwich) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7604CD05: Community Development Act Entitlement Grant (Town of Farmington) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7604CD06: Washington Street Rehabilitation Program - Innovative (Norwalk Redevelopment Agency) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7602CD03: New Haven Innovative Project Proposal for Neighborhood Preservation (City of New Haven) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7605CD02: South Central Conn. Innovative Project Rehabilitation Program (City of New Haven) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7605CD03: Community Development Block Grant Program - Entitlement Grant (Town of Glastonbury) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7605CD04: Community Development Block Grant Program - Second Year - Entitlement Grant (City of Middletown) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7605CD05: Housing & Neighborhood Preservation & Passenger Rail Mobility in the Capitol Region - Phase I (DCA) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7606CD01: Community Development Program - Entitlement Grant (Town of East Hartford) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7610CD01: DEP - Environmental Review Team - Innovative Project (Box 1)
      - CDA 7611CD01: City of Torrington Discretionary Grant (Box 1)
      - CDA 7611CD02: Regional Rehabilitation institute Areawide Program (City of New Haven) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7612CD01: City of New Britain - Discretionary Grant (Box 1)
      - CDA 7701CD01: Town of Bloomfield - 3rd Year Entitlement Grant (Box 1)
      - CDA 7701CD02: City of Ansonia Discretionary Grant (Box 1)
      - CDA 7701CD03: City of Ansonia Entitlement Grant (Box 1)
      - CDA 7701CD04: Town of Lisbon Discretionary Grant (Box 1)
      - CDA 7701CD05: City of Middletown Discretionary Grant (Box 1)
      - CDA 7701CD06: City of Willimantic Discretionary Grant (Box 1)
      - CDA 7701CD07: Town of Seymour Discretionary Grant - Senior Citizen's Center (Box 1)
      - CDA 7701CD08: Town of Seymour Discretionary Grant - Public Housing Conservation (Box 1)
      - CDA 7701CD09: Town of East Haven - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7701CD10: DCA - Areawide Program (Box 1)
      - CDA 7702CD02: City of New London - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 1)
      - CDA 7702CD03: City of Bridgeport - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD04: Town of Groton - Discretionary Grant (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD05: City of New Haven - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD04: Town of East Haven - Discretionary Grant (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD07: City of Willimantic - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD08: City of Waterbury - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD09: Town of Plainville - Discretionary Grant (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD10: Town of Windsor - Discretionary Grant (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD11: Town of East Hartford - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD12: Town of Vernon - Discretionary Grant - Reconstruction of the Rockville Sewer System (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD15: City of Norwalk - Discretionary Grant (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD16: City of Norwalk - Entitlement Grant (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD17: City of Derby - Discretionary Grant (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD18: City of Derby - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD19: City of Stratford - Discretionary Grant (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD20: Town of Tolland - Discretionary Grant (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD21: Town of Manchester - Entitlement Grant (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD22: Town of Portland - Discretionary Grant (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD23: Town of Newtown - Discretionary Grant (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD24: Town of Cheshire - Discretionary Grant (Box 2)
      - CDA 7702CD25: Town of Hamden - Discretionary Grant (Box 3)
      - CDA 7702CD26: Town of Stratford - Entitlement Grant (Box 3)
      - CDA 7703CD01: Town of East Haddam - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 3)
      - CDA 7703CD02: Town of Vernon - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 3)
      - CDA 7703CD03: Town of Enfield - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 3)
      - CDA 7703CD04: City of Danbury - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 3)
      - CDA 7703CD05: Town of Portland - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 3)
      - CDA 7704CD01: City of Meriden - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 3)
      - CDA 7704CD02: City of Middletown - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 3)
      - CDA 7704CD03: City of Bristol - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 3)
      - CDA 7704CD04: Town of Farmington - Entitlement Grant (Box 3)
      - CDA 7704CD05: City of Norwich - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 3)
      - CDA 7704CD06: Town of Fairfield - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 3)
      - CDA 7704CD07: City of New Britain - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 3)
      - CDA 7704CD08: Town of West Hartford - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 3)
      - CDA 7704CD09: City of Milford - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 3)
      - CDA 7705CD02: City of West Haven - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7705CD03: Town of Glastonbury - Entitlement Grant (3rd year) (Box 4)
  - General Files, 1976-1979; 1991-028
    Includes working papers and agency analysis of various state programs, policies, and events.
    - American Institute of Planners, 1978 (Box 1)
    - American Institute of Planners, 1977 April 1-October 31 (Box 1)
    - American Institute of Planners, 1976 January-June (Box 1)
    - A. I. P. - International City Management Association Committee (Box 1)
    - Census Material (Box 1)
    - Coastal Area Management, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Coastal Area Management, 1977 April 1-October 31 (Box 1)
    - Coastal Area Management, 1977 November-December (Box 1)
    - Coastal Area Management, 1977 January-February (Box 2)
    - Coastal Area Management, 1976 August-December (Box 2)
    - Coastal Area Management, 1976 May-July (Box 2)
    - Coastal Area Management, 1976 January-April (Box 2)
    - Coastal Area Management Advisory Board (Box 2)
    - CAM, 1976 (Box 2)
    - Coastal Zone Management (Box 2)
    - Commission on Connecticut's Future (Box 2)
    - Commission on Environmental Protection and Economic Development, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Conn. State energy Conservation Plan (Box 3)
    - Energy (Box 3)
    - Energy Conservation Plan (Box 3)
    - Council of State Planning Agencies, 1978 (Box 3)
    - Eastern CT Rural/Industrial Areas Preservation Comm. (Box 3)
    - Conn. Public Transportation Authority (Box 3)
    - Council of State Governments (Box 3)
    - CEPA (Box 3)
    - CEPA - Rocky Neck State Park (Box 3)
    - Connecticut Environmental Policy and Act (CEPA), 1977 (Box 3)
    - Connecticut State Energy Conservation Plan (Box 4)
      - F & C Purchasing Division (Box 4)
      - Dept. of Public Works (Box 4)
      - Dept. of Transportation (Box 4)
      - Correspondence other states (Box 4)
    - General correspondence, 1976-1979; 5 folders (Box 4)
    - Legislation (Box 4)
      - Conservation & Development (Box 4)
      - Proposed (Box 4)
      - Federal (Box 4)
    - Legislature (Box 4)
    - Long Island Sound Study - New York State (LISS-NY) (Box 4)
    - Metropolitan Reg. Council, Inc., 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Nat'l Assoc. of Regional Councils (NARC), 1976 January-August (Box 4)
    - National Governors' Association (Box 4)
    - New England River Basins Commission, 1977-1979; 11 inches (Box 5)
    - New England Regional Commission (Box 5)
    - Regional Planning Agencies, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Plan of Conservation and Development (Box 6)
    - State Planning Council (Box 6)
    - State Implementation Plan (SIP) for Air Quality (Box 6)
    - Regional Plan Association (Box 6)
    - State Planning Council Designees (Box 6)
    - State Planning Council (Box 6)
    - State Planning Council Minutes and Agenda (Box 6)
    - State Science, Engineering and Technology Program -SSET (Box 6)
    - Department's State Planning Council appointments (Box 6)
    - Water Quality Planning (208), 1979 (Box 6)
    - Thames River Study (Box 6)
    - Urban Task Force (Box 7)
      - Minutes of Meeting & Agendas (Box 7)
      - Subcomm. III Employment and Economic Development (Box 7)
      - Subcomm. IV Community Conservation & Development (Box 7)
    - Water Quality Planning (208), 1976-1978; 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Federal Agencies (Box 8)
      - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture Soil Conservation Service, 978 (Box 8)
      - U.S. Dept. of Energy Coal Conservation, 1977-1978 (Box 8)
      - U.S. Dept. of Environmental Protection, 1976-1978 (Box 8)
      - Federal Energy Admin, 1975-1977 (Box 8)
      - Federal Regional Council Energy Resource Development Task Force, 1976-1977; 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Federal Regional Council of New England, 1977 (Box 8)
      - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers (Box 8)
      - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
      - U.S. Bureau of the Census, 1978 (Box 8)
      - U.S. Dept of Commerce, 1976 (Box 8)
      - U.S. Dept. of Health, Education & Welfare, 1976-1979 (Box 8)
      - HUD 701 - Work Study, 1977-1978 (Box 8)
      - HUD forms (Box 8)
      - U.S. Dept. of Housing and Urban Development General, 1976-1979 (Box 8)
      - U.S. Housing & Urban Development CPA-CT-01-00-1074, 1979 (Box 8)
      - U.S. Dept. of Housing & Urban Development 701, 1976-1977; 3 folders (Box 8)
      - HUD/FEA proposed demo grant, 1976 (Box 8)
      - HUD grant application materials, 1975-1977 (Box 9)
      - U.S. Dept. of Housing and Urban Dev., 1978 (Box 9)
      - HUD DCA Indirects, 1974-1976 (Box 9)
      - HUD demonstration project CPA-CT-01-00-1051, 1976 (Box 9)
      - U.S. Dept. of Interior, 1979 (Box 9)
      - Office of Management & Budget Executive Office of the President, 1979 (Box 9)
      - U.S. Dept. of Transportation, 1979 (Box 9)
    - State Agencies (Box 9)
      - Dept. of Administrative Services, 1979 (Box 9)
      - Dept, of Agriculture, 1976-1978 (Box 9)
      - Attorney General's Office, 1977-1979 (Box 9)
      - Auditors, 1978 (Box 9)
      - City Liaison, 1976 (Box 9)
      - Civil Preparedness, 1976-1979 (Box 9)
      - Dept. of Community Affairs, 1977-1976 (Box 9)
      - Comptroller's Office, 1975-1979 (Box 9)
      - Dept. of Consumer Protection, 1979 (Box 9)
      - Day Care Office, 1979 (Box 9)
      - Dept. of Environmental Protection Grant Administration, 1975 (Box 9)
      - Board of Education, 1977-1978 (Box 9)
      - Dept. of Economic Development, 1979 (Box 9)
      - Dept. of Commerce, 1976-1978 (Box 9)
      - Dept. of Environmental Protection, 1979 (Box 9)
      - Dept. of Environmental Protection - Ad Hoc Air Quality Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
      - Dept. of Environmental Protection - Indian Affairs, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
      - Dept. of Environmental Protection, 1976-1977 (Box 9)
      - Dept. of Environmental Protection, 1978 (Box 10)
      - Council on Environmental Quality, 1979 (Box 10)
      - Governor's Office, 1976-1979 (Box 10)
      - Finance & Control, 1976-1977 (Box 10)
      - Governor's Office - Washington, 1976 (Box 10)
      - Dept. of Health, 1976-1978 (Box 10)
      - Health Delp. Task Force on Carcinogenic Substances, 1977 (Box 10)
      - Commission on Higher Education, 1975-1977 (Box 10)
      - Connecticut Historical Commission, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      - Commission on Human Rights & Opportunities, 1975-1979 (Box 10)
      - Office of Intergovernmental Programs, 1975-v1977 (Box 10)
      - Connecticut Justice Commission, 1977-1978 (Box 10)
      - Dept. of Labor, 1976-1977 (Box 10)
      - Council on Human Services, 1977 (Box 10)
      - Legislative Committee on State Planning & Development, 1976-1977 (Box 10)
      - Office of Legislative Research, 1978 (Box 10)
      - Connecticut State Library, 1976-1977 (Box 10)
      - Lieutenant Governor's Office, 1976-1977 (Box 10)
      - Dept. of Mental Health, 1979 (Box 10)
      - Office of Policy and Management, 1977-1979 (Box 11)
      - Office of Policy and Management (Box 11)
        - Capitol facilities & development plans, 1978 (Box 11)
        - Business office, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
        - CDP monthly reports, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
        - Comprehensive planning, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
        - Employment & Training Division, 1979 (Box 11)
        - Energy, 1977-1979 (Box 11)
        - Intergovernmental Relations, 1977-1978 (Box 11)
        - Meeting reports, 1977-1978 (Box 11)
        - Population Projections Project, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
      - Dept. of Planning & Energy Policy, 1975-1977 (Box 11)
      - Power Facilities Evaluation Council, 1976-1979 (Box 11)
      - Public Utilities Control Authority (PUCA), 1977 (Box 11)
      - Dept. of Public Works, 1976-1979 (Box 11)
      - National Register for Historical Places, 1979 (Box 11)
      - Connecticut Review Board for the National Register of Historic Places, 1979 June 7 (Box 11)
      - Office of the Secretary of the State, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
      - Dept. of Transportation (Box 11)
        - Commissioner's Office, 1977-1979 (Box 11)
        - Other than Commissioner's Office, 1977-1979 (Box 12)
        - Governor's Rail Advisory Task Force, 1977-1979 (Box 12)
        - I-91 Hartford to Enfield, 1975 (Box 12)
        - Northeast Rail Corridor, 1977 (Box 12)
        - Trumbull Airport Master Plan, 1978 (Box 12)
      - University of Connecticut, 1979 (Box 12)
      - State Planning Council Task Force - Water Company Lands, 1975-1977 (Box 12)
      - 4.13 General correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 12)
      - 4.13 Legal/Economic Subcommittee (General), 1976 (Box 12)
      - 4.13 Legislation, 1977 (Box 12)
      - 4.13 Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 12)
      - 4.13 Generic Hearings, 1976 (Box 12)
      - 4.13 Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 12)
      - Housing Cost Study, 1967-1972 (Box 12)
      - Executive order #3 General Correspondence, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Administrative Records, 1957-1991; 1996-030
    - Administrative Files (Box 1)
      - Central Naugatuck Valley Regional Planning Agency Correspondence (Box 1)
      - Naugatuck Valley (Box 1)
      - Naugatuck Valley Subcommittees (Box 1)
      - Valley Economic Unit Studies, Farmington & Naugatuck River Valleys (Box 1)
      - Naugatuck Valley Region, Industrial Sites Study Data Sheet File (Box 1)
    - News Clippings (Box 2)
      - General Publicity regional Newspaper Clips Book 2 (Box 2)
      - Central Connecticut Region Planning Agency, 1966-1969 (Box 2)
      - South Central Connecticut Planning Region, 1966-1968 (Box 2)
      - Capitol Region, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
      - Northeastern Connecticut & QVAC Planning Region, 1967 (Box 2)
      - Connecticut River Estuary Planning Region, 1966 (Box 2)
      - Housatonic Valley Planning Region, 1967 (Box 2)
      - Windham Region, 1966-1969 (Box 2)
      - Southeastern Connecticut Region, 1966 (Box 2)
      - Southeastern Connecticut Region, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
      - Southeastern Connecticut Region, 1969 (Box 2)
      - Valley Regional Planning Agency (formerly Ansonia/Derby), 1966-1968 (Box 2)
      - Southeastern Region, 1966-1969 (Box 2)
      - South Central Connecticut Regional Planning Agency, 1969 (Box 2)
      - Northeastern Connecticut Planning Region & QVAC, 1966, 1968 (Box 2)
      - Midstate Planning Region, 1966-1969 (Box 2)
      - Litchfield Hills Regional Planning Agency (formerly Torrington/Winchester), 1966-1969 (Box 2)
      - Housatonic Valley Regional Planning Agency, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
      - Greater Bridgeport Planning Region, 1966-1969 (Box 2)
      - Connecticut River Estuary Region, 1967-1969 (Box 2)
      - Housatonic Valley Planning Region, 1966 (Box 2)
      - Northwestern Connecticut Planning Region, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
      - Housatonic Valley, 1968 (Box 2)
      - Capitol Region Planning Agency, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
      - General Publicity Regional Book 3, 1966 (Box 2)
      - CDC & Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
      - General Publicity Regional Book 4, 1967 (Box 2)
      - CDC & Miscellaneous, 1965-1967 (Box 2)
    - Administrative Files (Box 3)
      - Naugatuck Valley (Box 3)
      - Norwich-New London-Groton material (Box 3)
      - Quinnebaug Valley (Box 3)
      - Southwestern Regional Planning Agency (Box 3)
      - Valley Regional Planning Agency (formerly Ansonia/Derby) (Box 3)
      - Windham Regional Planning Agency (Box 3)
      - Greater Bridgeport Regional Planning Agency (Box 4)
      - Southeastern Connecticut Regional Planning Agency (Box 4)
    - Correspondence (Box 5)
      - Terry Schnure, James Palma, Maria Buatti, and George Pohorilak, 1981 January-June (Box 5)
      - Terry Schnure, James Palma, Maria Buatti, and George Pohorilak, 1981 July-December (Box 5)
      - Gail B. Promboin, Robert W. Grant, 1981 (Box 5)
      - Terry Schnure, James Palma, Maria Buatti, and George Pohorilak, 1982 January-June (Box 5)
      - Terry Schnure, Maria Buatti, James Palma, Bill Cox, Bill Kraynak, 1982 July-December (Box 5)
      - Terry Schnure, Maria Buatti, James Palma, Bill Kraynak, Bill Cox, 1983 January-June (Box 5)
      - Terry Schnure, Maria Buatti, James Palma, Bill Kraynak, Bill Cox, and Horace Brown, 1983 July-December (Box 5)
      - Terry Schnure, Maria Buatti, James Palma, Bill Kraynak, Bill Cox, and Horace Brown, 1984 January-June (Box 5)
    - HUD applications and correspondence, 1971 July 1-1972 June 30 (Box 6)
    - PDPD, Human Services Central Files, Maps (Box 7)
    - Administrative Files (Box 8)
      - Planning Region Definition Studies. Summary Binder II - Commutation, 1957-1958 (Box 8)
        Individual binder containing Town of Residence Summary Sheets and commutation study summary reports and maps.
      - Bi-weekly reports to the Governor, 1981-1991 (Box 8)
- Series 14. Management and Justice Planning Division, 1979-1987; 1989-069; 16 cubic feet
  - Subject Files
    There is no box 1 or box 5.
    - Reports (Box 2)
      - Admissions Task force, 1979 (Box 2)
      - Caucus on Black Aged, 1982 (Box 2)
      - Odd/Even Energy Emergency, 1979 (Box 2)
      - FMIS, 1979-1983 (Box 2)
      - Forensic Services Advisory Comm., 1971 (Box 2)
      - Gengras Commission, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
      - Human Services Reorganization, 1978 (Box 2)
      - Institutional Care, 1979 (Box 2)
      - Job Specifications, 1978 (Box 2)
      - National Conference on Research, Demonstration and Evaluation in Public Social Services, 1979 (Box 2)
      - Racial Harmony, 1982 (Box 2)
      - Technology Transfer Forum and Exhibition, 1979 (Box 2)
      - Urban Action Task Force, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
    - Compensation Study, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Compensation Study, 1983 (Box 3)
    - Oral Exam/Transportation manager, 1978-1979 (Box 3)
    - Bureau of Purchasing (Box 3)
      - Courier Services, 1980 (Box 3)
      - Centralized Advertising (Box 3)
      - Gas Coupon Rationing, 1984 (Box 3)
      - Electric Coast Containment, 1983 (Box 3)
      - Federal Donated Food, 1983 (Box 3)
      - Food Management, 1982 (Box 3)
      - New Vehicle Purchase, 1979-1980 (Box 3)
      - Regional Laundry, 1981 (Box 3)
      - USPS Direct Delivery, 1983 (Box 3)
    - AG & DAS - Delinquent Accounts, 1984 (Box 3)
    - AG - Blue Ribbon Commission, 1983 (Box 3)
    - DCYS - Foster Care, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Consumer Protection - Management Study, 1979 (Box 3)
    - education - State Education Management Project, 1981 (Box 3)
    - MVD (Box 4)
      - Delinquent Parking Tickets, 1983 (Box 4)
      - Evaluation of PA 79-577, Mandatory Insurance Laws, 1979 (Box 4)
      - License Plates, 1978 (Box 4)
    - OPM (Box 4)
      - General, 1978-1984 (Box 4)
      - Budget, 1980-1985 (Box 4)
      - Budget Summary Status Reports, 1982 (Box 4)
      - AA Advisory Committee, 1980-1985 (Box 4)
      - Employee Suggestions, 1985 (Box 4)
      - Essential Services Study, 1983 (Box 4)
      - Federal Budget Impact Analysis, 1985 (Box 4)
      - Issue Papers, 1982 (Box 4)
    - Motor Vehicle Study, 1981 (Box 4)
    - OPM Management Task Force, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
    - Management Seminar, 1985 (Box 4)
    - Management Analysts Conference, 1982 (Box 4)
    - Management Analysts Conference, 1983 (Box 4)
    - GOV & OPM Significant Programs and Efforts, 1984 (Box 4)
    - M & E CRESAP Study, 1982 (Box 4)
    - Hospital Costs, 1984 (Box 4)
    - Originals - OPM RFP Program Budget, 1982 February (Box 6)
    - OPM Program Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
    - Program Budget, 1985 (Box 6)
    - Program Budget Project, 1985 (Box 6)
    - Policy Team, 1979 (Box 6)
    - M & E Monthly Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 6)
    - M & E Biweekly Reports for Governor, 1981-1984 (Box 6)
    - Management Task Force, 1980 (Box 6)
    - DPUC - Transportation Division, 1983 (Box 6)
    - DRS - Motor Carrier Tax, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Secretary of the State, 1983 (Box 6)
    - DOT (Box 6)
      - Bureau of Highways, 1979 (Box 6)
      - Traffic Accident Reporting, 1979 (Box 6)
    - DAS - Bureau of Purchasing, Standardization Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 6)
    - Uncas File (Box 7)
      Includes petitions, letters, minutes
    - OPM Administrative Office, 1987 (Box 8)
    - OPM, 1985-1987 (Box 8)
    - OPM Administrative Office, 1986 (Box 8)
    - EEO Affirmative Action, 1985-1987 (Box 8)
    - OPM AA Contract Compliance, 1986-1987 (Box 8)
    - Administration of Medication, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Administration of Medication, 1986-1987 (Box 8)
    - OPM Affirmative Action, 1985 (Box 8)